The Copyist is a drama film directed by Basil Coleman.
A fateful day in the life of a great composer.
A play with music
The Composer, played by Dinsdale Landen.
The Copyist, played by Peter Egan.
Heinrich Schalleplatte, played by Joseph O'Conor.
Wolfgang Schalleplatte, played by Tony Anholt.
Walter, played by Eugene Schlusser.
Tina, played by Eileen Helsby.
Grease: The Original Soundtrack from the Motion Picture is the
original motion picture soundtrack for the 1978 film Grease.
It was originally released by RSO Records and subsequently
re-issued by Polydor Records between 1984 and 1991.
It has sold over 30 million copies worldwide, making it one of the best-selling albums of all
time, also ranking amongst the biggest selling soundtrack albums of all time.
The song "You're the One That I Want" was a U.S.
1 for stars John Travolta and Olivia Newton-John.
Besides performers John Travolta and Olivia Newton-John, the album also featured songs by rock and roll revival group Sha Na Na as well as the hit song
"Grease", a tune written by Barry Gibb (of the Bee Gees) and sung by Frankie Valli (of The Four Seasons) that was an additional U.S.